♪ Words on the lips, yeah
I'm the latest gem ♪
♪ Oh, have you heard? I'm at it again... ♪
[Heather] Ooh.
-Looks amazing.
-[gasps] Look at it!
♪ I'm taking over... ♪
[Heather] Look!
-[Mary] This turned out... the waterfall.
-So beautiful.
[Heather] Oh, my gosh.
♪ Everybody's gonna know
Everybody's gonna see ♪
♪ Everywhere I turn all eyes on me ♪
♪ Float like a butterfly
Sting like a bee ♪
♪ 'Cause everywhere I go
All eyes on me... ♪
[Heather] This is so incredible.
-It turned out so amazing.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Jason was not lying, was he?
-No, not at all.
[Heather] Oh, my God, Mary.
♪ I got the buzz... ♪
[Heather] Look at that pool!
Last time I was here,
I was jumping in the pool with no water.
[Mary] Oh, my God. Yeah.
And walking the whole thing...
-This is more refreshing now.
-This is so much more refreshing.
[Heather] This is such a vacation oasis.
[Mary] We need to sell this
to someone we know,
so we can just be like,
"Pool party today."
"Can we come over and party
at your house? Yeah, okay."
-Wait, there's Chrishell.
-Yeah.
♪ Everybody put your hands up ♪
♪ Girls round the world ♪
♪ Put your crown on, ha ♪
♪ Poppin' ma knee with the champagne ♪
♪ Poppin', go dance on ♪
♪ Drippin' my bleach, no C Cane ♪
♪ They mad, got them on ♪
-Oh, hi!
-Yay!
-[Mary] Hi. You're finally here!
-[Chrishell] Hi.
-Walk the catwalk.
-[Chrishell] What?
[Heather] Strut it.
Strut it. Strut it. Yeah.
[Mary] In this house you gotta work it.
-Hi.
-[Heather] Triple hug.
-Hello.
-[Heather] What do you think?
-This is crazy.
-[Heather chuckles]
-I'm dying to see that master closet.
♪ Hey, you ♪
[Heather] Wow!
[Chrishell] Is this the master right here?
[Heather] This is the master!
[gasps] Oh, my gosh!
-[Heather] What is going on here?
-[Mary] Unreal.
I have a pretty nice closet,
but this is like...
[Heather] Yeah,
this is just another level.
And look at this, look at the view.
[Chrishell] You could literally look out
to see what the weather is like.
I feel like if you had this closet you'd
have to talk like this, "Hello, darling."
[Heather] Hello, darling.
[Heather] Wait, is that new?
[Mary] That's astroturf...
-[Heather] Are you serious?
-Yes.
The owner put astroturf on the roof
of his neighbor's home.
A mere couple hundred grand, I'm sure.
[Heather] Master bedroom.
Oh, my God.
-[Chrishell] Wow!
-[Mary] This turned out awesome.
[Heather] This is beautiful.
♪ I'm a big, big deal ♪
[Heather] It takes the right type
of person to buy this house.
It's not gonna be just the average
person walking on the street.
You have to have a lot of money.
-Shall we see this bathroom?
-[Mary] Yes.
[Heather] This bathtub...
[Chrishell] I think your shit really
wouldn't stink if you had this bathroom.
It would come out wrapped in cellophane.
Pink scented cellophane. Wrapped.
I can't wait to see the rooftop.
Oh, yes.
-Right?
-I forgot.
Oh, let's go look.
[Mary] This is so cool.
♪ Got me feelin' like... ♪
[Chrishell] Oh, wow!
[Heather] This view. I love it.
Amazing.
[Chrishell] Every single detail
of this house is crazy.
Just stuff you'll never see anywhere else.
[Heather] Okay, I am hot. Shall we go?
[Chrishell] Sit downstairs
and hang out for a minute?
♪ Got me feelin' like ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
[Chrishell]
What would you do with all this space?
You'd have to walkie-talkie to someone.
If I had this house,
you girls would be here all the time.
-Oh, I would just live out here.
-[Heather chuckles]
I'd live in your closet.
[laughing] Yes.
So what's going on ladies?
I heard Christine got engaged.
Have you guys met him?
-[Mary] No.
-[Heather] I haven't.
Oh, you guys haven't...
Right, because she's been out of town.
She's been out of town a lot.
Christine's been working at the
Oppenheim Group way longer than I have.
But I'm not sure why,
ever since I started working there,
we just never really got along.
She can sit on the floor
until she proves herself.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I feel like you don't own up
to the things that you say
and that's where this is coming from.
What you say about other people.
You need a little hug right now.
Honestly, how pathetic is she?
[Davina] Unnecessarily dramatic.
-When I ask you, "What did you say..."
-[Chrishell] Don't yell at me.
Christine, I talked to Mary
about what I said.
But when I asked you at the dinner,
you conveniently didn't remember.
You understand the difference, right,
or do you still have dementia?
Christine...
I can usually get along with anyone,
but this one...
It's probably not going to happen.
I didn't even find out from her.
I didn't either.
It was so fast.
Everyone's like,
"Oh, Christine's engaged."
I texted her, "Hey, have something
you wanna tell me?" She's like, "What?"
-What?
-I was like, "Um..."
"Something about, like, an engagement?"
And she's like, "Oh, yeah."
Just, like, nothing, like they were...
I'm like,
"Honey, that's kind of big news."
If, like, my best friend didn't tell me
she was engaged,
I'd be, like, really hurt actually,
you know? I don't know.
How do you feel, like, really?
It's just odd to me that she...
didn't say anything. I had to ask her.
But I mean, we've kind of
grown apart a little bit.
Christine and I used to be
very, very close.
I don't know what has happened
to cause a rift in our relationship.
But, it's so strange.
She gets engaged
and she didn't share that with me.
It makes me feel sad and confused.
Well, how did they meet?
Christine and-- What's his name?
-Oh, Christian.
-Christian!
He was her client.
-Oh!
-[Mary] Yeah.
She was showing him properties.
I think he was dating
someone else at the time.
Really?
And somehow she just clicked with him
and they got together.
That would make me so nervous though,
because if somebody cheats for you,
-that means they would cheat on you.
-I don't know...
♪ Whoa, oh. Whoa, oh. Whoa, oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Watch me move
Watch me how I work it ♪
♪ Shoulders back
Because I know I'm worth it ♪
♪ I walk with swagger
Because I know I own it ♪
♪ I'mma strut, I'mma strut
Whoa-oh-oh ♪
I am back.
I have a new man, I have a new ring,
I have a new house,
and I'm ready to dominate the market.
♪ Watch out
Here I come now ♪
♪ I'm gonna rock this house
Like no one before ♪
♪ I'm gonna burn it down
With fire and gold ♪
♪ I'm gonna stand up, stand up ♪
♪ Whoa-oh-oh ♪
♪ Light it up, light it up ♪
Okay, I know we're not poor, so can
we turn the air conditioning on in here.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, my gosh, it's so weird to be back.
-I miss being on vaca--
-[Christian] You miss being on vacation?
Christian and were traveling the world,
I took a break
because I just sold
a six-million dollar house.
And we were all over. We went to
the Maldives, Bordeaux, Capri...
I feel like I was traveling the world
doing my Eat, Pray, Love thing.
But in five-star resorts, always.
[chuckles]
I'm really excited to be back because
I'm excited for everyone to meet you.
-Yeah.
-Christian is big in the tech world.
He went to MIT,
and he's a software engineer,
and has worked on multiple companies,
multiple development projects.
And he's retired,
but my job is really important.
And the Oppenheim Group's best agent
is back in town.
-[Christine] I should probably call Jason.
-[Christian] Okay.
-Tell him I'm back in town. [chuckles]
-[ringing tone]
[Jason on phone]
Hey, what's up, Christine?
Hi Jason, how are you?
-[Jason] I'm good.
-I am back in town.
I'm ready to be back in the grind
and hustling again.
[Jason] Great. I'm glad you've been
out there enjoying the world,
but, let's be honest, Kings Road has still
been sitting on the market since you left.
I know it's sitting on the market,
I've been on top of my job.
Just because I'm not in office proximity
doesn't mean that I'm not doing my job.
There's been times
where we've been on vacation
and I flew back if I had
someone that was interested.
So if something ever came up, I would
fly back and take care of my listing.
So don't worry, I got this.
Kings Road is under control
and I'm going to sell this thing.
Good. Listen, we're all happy
to have you back.
-See you when you get here.
-All right. Bye, Jason.
♪ Wow. Uh-huh ♪
♪ So cool it's the talk of the town ♪
[Christine] About a month and a half
after we started dating,
I was showing Christian houses.
I actually used to have
the listing on our house
and I used to do open houses.
I would sit in that open house
every Sunday
and I would picture myself
living in that house,
getting coffee with my husband,
and I now live in the house
that I envisioned myself living in.
I snatched that up.
-[Christine] Oh. So nice to be back.
-Yeah.
[Christine gasps]
Hi, my little teddy bear!
-Hi, teddy bear!
-[dog barking]
How have you been, little boy?
♪ Oh, oh, oh!  ♪
♪ Start a fire, turn it up ♪
♪ Let the world know ♪
♪ Shine like gold ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh!
Shine like... ♪
[Heather] Look at him looking at you.
Cookie.
[Maya] I was pushing for two hours.
Uh, he didn't want to come out.
And they shot the epidural for me.
[Heather] Wait, they did what?
They shot what?
The epidural.
-What is that?
-The epidural?
Epidural?
-[Heather] You wanna sit?
-[Maya] Yeah.
Unfortunately,
I had a long night at the hospital
with a very painful delivery.
And a vacuum delivery at the end,
because baby Aiden
was comfortable inside
and he didn't want to come out.
So, can you just imagine
a vacuum from your vagina?
It was pretty much a nightmare.
You feel like someone is digging inside,
it was awful.
-[Maya] Hey, buddy.
-I'm so excited to meet you.
-Do you like blondes?
-You can hold him.
[Maya] See, he's smiling to you.
-You like the blonde girl?
-[Aiden giggles]
-See? He's relaxed with you, I mean...
-Who's a baby?
You're good, girl. You're ready.
-[Heather] Oh! Spit up.
-[Maya] Oh, shit.
-Holy moly.
-I know.
I'm so excited to see Maya as a mom.
I'm just so proud of her
and her struggles with getting pregnant
and the miscarriages.
So to see her as a mom and she finally got
everything that she's been hoping for,
I'm so happy for her.
And Aiden is so cute.
I tried to look on Instagram to see
what's going on in your life
and text you guys, but it's hard.
I was in a weird zone, too
because it was like,
going through a breakup and then dating,
I've been in this, like, bubble of love.
You didn't tell me, girl, and then
I see you on TMZ, I'm like...
[Heather] It happened really fast with us,
and we just, like--
He's literally my best friend.
So how did you guys meet?
Fourth of July.
His boat was parked next
to the boat I was on down in Newport.
-Really?
-And my girlfriend
just happened to be on his boat.
I jumped on his boat and he turned around
and he was like, "Hi, I'm Tarek."
Then we were just texting
and kept in touch.
On our first date, it was just like...
-[Maya] Magic?
-It was like...
I found him very endearing
and very, like, kind and real.
I feel, like, really good.
We've been dating for about a month.
So it definitely moved very quick.
But we both said that when we're together
the world stops.
I feel like I've known him for years.
Doesn't feel like it's only been a month.
Bu when you know, you know, right?
And how are things at the office?
Christine's situation was--
So, wait. I missed everything.
Like, I'm in Miami, right?
I was in Sweden. [laughing]
So, I get a call from Davina,
saying, "You heard
that Christine is engaged?"
I'm like, "What? Engaged?"
I'm like, "Wait a minute.
I saw Christine in December.
-And she said she's dating this guy..."
-The younger guy.
Yeah! But then, I guess she met Christian,
and two months later in February, I get...
-Engaged.
-Yeah.
It's funny, she judged Mary
for rushing with Romain.
I'm shocked, but I'm so happy for her
and her ring is freaking stunning.
What's going on with
Christine and Chrishell?
Are they still kind of like, not talking?
Well...
It makes me so uncomfortable
because I just feel the tension.
I don't know how to...
-...deal with it. Yeah.
-Between the two?
I feel like it's just time to--
It's been so long now.
I don't even think at this point
they know what they're fighting about.
Like, it's done, it's over.
Mary's not even mad about anything,
and it was about Mary.
-That's the funny thing.
-Shouldn't Mary be the one upset?
I know, that's the whole thing.
Christine was fighting about Mary,
Mary doesn't even care.
And it's been a couple of months,
and I mean, we all have the same goals.
To sell houses and
actually do real estate.
-You know?
-Yeah.
-[baby groaning]
-He's getting fussy, girl.
-Is he? Okay.
-Yeah.
-Ready to bounce?
-I want him, he's so cute, Maya.
-He's a good baby.
But honestly, I'm excited to come to
the office and dress up,
and not have clothes
with my baby spit on it.
-[Heather gasps]
-Yeah, sorry about that girl.
Send me the bill for the dry clean.
[both laughing]
♪ Oh, oh
See the future with my head up high ♪
♪ Like a flame on my mind, I multiply ♪
[engine roaring]
Do you guys always get kicked off
the Wi-Fi? It's really frustrating.
Ooh! Oh, my goodness, I just...
slid into my desk.
[Brett] Chrishell, I've got your husband
on my desk.
Okay, not this one right?
[Brett laughing] Nice plug.
[Chrishell] I got my reading materials.
We should put pictures
of our men on our desks.
Thank God I'm married to him,
because I would be like, "Oh, my God."
[Mary] Is that weird to think that
there are some teenage girls that actually
have his picture up on their wall?
-No, I think it's, like, a compliment.
-[Mary] Yeah.
[Mary] It's cute.
Yeah. Because it's like,
"I know where he sleeps." [chuckles]
Most nights.
Oh, Brett, you're just jealous because
you've got the rotating door going on.
Not anymore.
I'm a one-woman man for the last 48 hours.
A one-woman man?
Forty-eight hours.
Who's the girl?
[Brett] This girl from the party
hasn't left yet.
You've allowed her to stay for this long?
[Brett] Yeah.
I mean, she'll be gone tomorrow, forever.
[laughing]
I mean,
this is your longest relationship ever.
No, Ernestine, my housekeeper.
Four years, three years.
Oh, my gosh.
-[Chrishell] Do you have a second?
-Yeah, sure.
I wanna talk to you about
something real quick.
[Chrishell] I'm excited to tell you.
Um, I know you always joke
about needing to have a passport
to go to the Valley,
but I feel like it's constant construction
and there's a lot of new builds.
I feel like,
why don't I focus a little more over there
'cause I already know the area,
I live there.
I know the school system.
My husband Justin and I just bought
our dream home in the Valley
and we love it so much.
It's like this modern farmhouse
that really feels like
an oasis outside of the city
and it's something that I never
really even dreamed of.
We realized, this is where it's at.
I'm big on the Valley.
I've been hearing about it,
but the price points are going up.
It used to be one, two-million dollar
sales and now I'm seeing
three, four, five, six, seven,
ten-million dollar sales out there.
-Right.
-You've been looking at developments?
-Yeah, I've actually been--
-You have a positive take?
Not knocking, because some of them
don't have doors,
but I'll see a construction site and I'll
go up and drop off some material.
I've yet to get a listing, but I wanna get
one of these new builds.
One builder is doing like
seven things normally,
so I'm trying to get my foot in the door.
There's really no brokerage controlling
a lot of the business out there.
So I think we can go out there,
do what we do over here,
and I think everyone
will love us out there.
We need you to be
the front person for this.
That'd be great. I would really love that.
Okay, so the Valley might not be
as cool to Jason and Brett
as the sexy Hollywood Hills,
but there are a lot of commissions.
Really good commissions
that you can make
on the other side of the hill.
I'm going to keep driving around
and trying to get listing appointments
with the different developers.
Listen, if you can get
one foot in the door,
then I'll drive over there
and we'll close it.
Did you think you'd ever say that?
You used to make fun of me
-for thinking the Valley was cool.
-That's why you're here.
I'm seriously withholding a lot of jokes
about the Valley now because I'm--
-See?
-I'm far more about it.
Wait, so hold on a second,
are you saying...
Was I right?
-I will--
-[Brett] We don't need to go that far.
I'm really glad you talked about this,
because this is more exciting for me
than for you.
I'm up for the challenge.
-Yeah, thank you. We're on the same page.
-I love it.
♪ You better get ready
Because I'm breaking out? ♪
♪ You better get ready for what I got ♪
♪ If you ain't ready
You ain't keeping up ♪
[Amanza] Ooh!
Honey, I'm home.
-Wow! [chuckles]
-[Mary] Right?
[Amanza] Mary,
I'm glad you have to hop out.
[Mary] Yeah, Jason...
Why did we not bring the Rolls?
[Jason] This is the Rolls Royce
of Broncos.
[Mary] You're going to have to wear heels
one day so you have to actually do this.
[Mary] Jason has wanted this Bronco
for his whole life basically
and he spent like $200,000
restoring it and getting it built
custom to exactly his taste.
[Amanza] I'm already sweating.
If I had $200,000
to just throw at something
then it would most definitely be a house.
But you know how boys are,
they love their toys.
[Jason] So Amanza, sometimes you have
to preview a property for your client.
So that's what Mary and I are doing here.
Make sure the floor plan is good,
make sure the views are good,
it's private, things like that,
before our client wastes his time.
I met Mary and Jason 19 years ago.
I know.
Oh, my God, we're so old.
I'm so grateful for Jason.
When I got a divorce,
he literally co-signed for an apartment
for me and my kids.
I was getting turned down right and left.
He was like, "As long as you pay
the rent on time, it's fine."
I've been doing interior design
for about eight years.
I was designing homes and staging homes
for the Oppenheim Group.
But now, I literally just got
my real estate license
and now here I am, trying to learn
everything that they all know.
[Jason] Well, this is sexy.
-[Mary] This is really nice.
-[Amanza] Whoa!
That's not contemporary,
that's a Tuscan Mediterranean.
-It's not contemporary.
-Oh!
[Jason] Oh.
-Are you okay?
-My shoe is stuck in the thingy.
-Oh, my God.
-Did you really get stuck?
-[Mary] Leave it to Amanza.
-[Amanza] Oh, my God.
[Amanza] It was one of my first meetings
to meet another agent, like,
outside the Oppenheim Group,
and I almost bite it.
Like, right in front of this
bougie big-time agent.
She got her heel stuck in the deck
at Beverly Glen.
[Mary laughing]
-Gotta be the center of attention.
-[Jason laughs]
I could've just been barefoot
and been real comfy, you know?
[chuckles]
This would've been easy.
-Only me.
-[Shawn] Talk to you later.
Okay.
You know the chances of that happening
are, like, one in a million.
-[Amanza] Nice to meet you.
-[Mary] Nice to see you.
-I'm the graceful one, Amanza.
-Shawn Elliot.
-Nice to meet you. How are you?
-How are you? Good to see you, man.
Thank you for getting us up here.
[Jason] So we're previewing for a client,
as you know.
We have a celebrity client
looking for privacy.
Listen to me, at five million and 750,
find me a better house in Bel Air.
Doesn't exist.
All right, let's take a look.
-[Mary] Great.
-[Jason] I like the open kitchen.
This island can double as a bar
and you could have a couple bartenders.
Guests could line up to get
their tequila shots, right?
-[Mary] How many bedrooms?
-Four bedrooms.
And five and a half bathrooms.
One of the nicest features of this house
is this open living area.
[Jason] This is a nice room.
-[Mary] Wow.
-That's a stunning piano.
-[Shawn] That piano...
-[Amanza] Antique?
...doesn't come with the house,
but that's a 1950 Steinway.
That's a $150,000 piano.
-Oh, it definitely comes with the house.
-[Shawn laughing]
[Jason] I do like how the master
is right off the living room.
Especially for a bachelor,
you want everything in the same open area.
Right. Entertain in the kitchen
and then maybe
depending on the bachelor,
entertain in the...
-In the bedroom.
-Yeah, right.
Look at the views of my Bronco.
I'm a little excited.
-This is not about you, all right?
-It's only been six months with it.
[both] This is your longest relationship.
[all laughing]
Come check out the master bathroom.
You have dueling showers,
separate water closets...
[Jason] Water closets? What?
-Toilets.
-[Jason] I was just testing Amanza.
Mary, you could shower in here,
your fiancé could shower in there.
[Mary] There you go.
Romain's French, he doesn't shower.
-[Mary] Oh!
-[Shawn laughing]
So guys, why don't you take a look at
the rest of the house on your own,
and then get back to me.
[Mary] Sounds good, thank you.
So, Amanza.
We have to teach you.
This is a learning experience.
[Amanza] I decided to start my real estate
career to better provide for my family.
I have two amazing kids.
I've been a single mom since they were one
and two, they're now eight and nine.
When I met my ex-husband,
he was playing in the NFL.
It was pretty comfortable.
When we separated,
my ex, unfortunately,
couldn't even pay child support.
I was doing everything.
I cleaned houses,
I walked dogs, I was being a nanny,
I hadn't cleaned my own toilet
in nine years,
and suddenly I'm scrubbing toilets
so that I can feed my kids.
It was a very humbling experience,
to say the least.
A good friend of mine said,
"Figure out your passion."
Eventually, I put everything
that I had into real estate.
Now with Jason, I'm trying to get used
to the whole boss-employee relationship.
I wanna take this opportunity for Mary
and I to show you the detail we look at.
I always want you to pick up
how much they spent on the house.
I'm really good at looking.
I need to practice selling.
[Jason] Okay, what do you notice
about these doors, for example?
[Amanza] The pocket doors?
[Jason] They're not pocket,
so those are accordion.
Less expensive than sliders.
-Next question.
-[Jason] Okay, next.
What do you notice about these floors?
-They're very clean.
-Well...
[Mary chuckling]
Every panel is seven feet long
and eleven inches wide.
That's very expensive.
The wider and longer, the more expensive.
So the little stuff...
[Amanza laughing]
This is important shit, man.
-I'm listening!
-Okay.
What do you notice about the appliances?
They're stainless steal. Sub-zero...
Yeah, good quality. Good quality stuff.
Okay, example...
[Amanza] That's a wine cellar.
-[Jason] Yes...
-[Mary] She's good.
But importantly,
it's not temperature controlled.
-You can see there's no unit in here.
-Right.
So you can never...
This is a fake wine cellar.
[Jason] What do you call this pool?
Um, "Jim."
What?
-Jim. I'd call him Jim.
-Well... [chuckling]
It's an infinity pool.
Christ, Jason, I know some things.
[Jason] So annoying. [laughing]
I think I know everything now.
I'm going to go and sell a house.
[laughing] Thank you, guys, very much.
♪ The more that I get
The less that I know ♪
[engine revs loudly]
[Jason] Just put,
"All outdoor furniture slash lamps."
[Amanza] It feels better in here.
-Oh, much better.
-It's so hot.
-[Mary] Hey, girls.
-[Maya] Hey!
-Hi, honey.
-Everybody is so colorful.
Hey, guys. That's just bad judgment,
there's a difference.
I spent my first night in
my new condo last night.
Oh, did you? How was it?
It was fun. It was awesome.
-So you're gonna stay there, or...
-I think so, yeah.
-Can I come see it?
-Yeah.
-Can I move in?
-When are you doing a party actually?
Two bedrooms aren't working,
bathroom's not working.
The bedrooms aren't working?
I was just trying to get her,
so she doesn't ask to move in,
but then I stuck my foot in my mouth.
I'll cook for you in the morning.
I'll make you eggs.
[Maya] Like, a vegan breakfast.
I'm vegan, so for me to say that...
Is Harley at a doggie sitter?
Or what did you...
This weekend my boyfriend's parents
are watching him.
You're calling him boyfriend.
-Yes, haven't you...
-[Brett] Okay.
[Maya] They've been moving so slow,
you know? One month.
Yeah, you're moving real slow.
Where have you been sleeping?
Under a rock?
My first time hearing it.
Oh, do you now that he dated my ex?
-Okay, he did not date your ex.
-[Brett] Really?
He went on one date with the girl.
He went on eight dates,
sorry, I'm just saying.
Are we gonna start this again
with my new boyfriend?
I just think it's a small world
that I saw an article about it.
I'm not talking shit.
[Brett] Heather, we need to catch up
on this relationship thing.
I'm learning more and more every time
I talk to somebody.
-Are you jealous?
-[Brett chuckles]
I was single for a short amount of time,
-you could've swooped...
-You were single for four hours.
-[Davina] Hey, ladies!
-[Brett] Like noon to 4 p.m..
[Davina] Hey, guys.
-[Maya] Hey, Davina.
-Hi. Hi.
Hi, I'm going to have Amanza sit here
if that's okay?
-[Davina] Okay. Okay.
-I'm kind of showing her the ropes.
[Maya] Wait, if Amanza is the new girl,
shouldn't she sit somewhere else?
-New girl?
-[Mary] She's not new.
[Mary] She's just a new agent.
She's not new.
[laughing] Don't make me take
my earrings off, Maya.
So, is Chrishell coming?
She's coming at some point.
No, I think she said she's--
I don't know.
[Heather] Maybe later?
I think she's in the Valley,
who knows, passing out cards
or going door to door.
Totally.
♪ Yeah! This is my world ♪
♪ Woo ♪
♪ I've been busy
Only working all day long, man ♪
♪ I'm hustling every day ♪
Ooh! I see one coming up.
♪ Mess with me on my block, yeah ♪
♪ I've got this thing on lock, yeah
Got swag... ♪
Hi, how are you?
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
-I'm barging in.
-Okay.
So with real estate, you can't
wait around for the phone to ring.
You have to hustle because we are
100 percent commission based.
So we have to create business.
Hi, this is Chrishell Hartley.
I am with the Oppenheim Group.
I'm actually outside
of your property on--
That sounds kind of creepy,
but I see that you guys are
under construction
and I just wanted to offer my services,
I would love to talk to you.
There is so much new development
in the Valley.
So, a strategy I have has been just
to drive around and see
these different construction sites,
trying to get in touch with the developer.
Here's actually the last listing
that I just sold in the Valley.
Above ask.
♪ Welcome to my world ♪
Well, they're definitely going
to need a realtor.
♪ Hello to my life ♪
♪ It's taking over
And there's no time to waste  ♪
♪ Got that feeling
Good, good feeling ♪
♪ Better get moving
Or I won't hesitate ♪
♪ Light it up
Here we go ♪
♪ Turn it up, let it go
Get ready ♪
[Mary] Over a hundred-something people
and I was like, "That's not--
To me, that's small."
-Hey, guys!
-[Mary] Or that's big, to me.
[Christine] Hi!
I'm back.
[Christine] How are you?
Good to see you, babe.
Hi, honey!
-[Christine] Oh, my God, Mary!
-Where are my souvenirs?
Where are my souvenirs?
Your souvenir is love, I'm sorry.
I'll just give you some sugar.
[Christine] Hi, babe.
Now, Christine is back at the office
finishing all of her glamorous vacations,
like Christopher Columbus,
doing the whole globe pretty much.
I actually wonder if she's going to
get back into the real estate game.
I don't know, I think she's addicted
to travel at this point.
-[Heather] Welcome back, honey.
-Hi!
-[Davina chuckling]
-You're all over Instagram
and your travels.
Feels good to be back in the office.
I'm excited to get back to work,
but I'm not gonna lie.
Like they say, "There's too many
cooks in the kitchen,"
there's too many bitches in this office.
[Christine] So nice to be back!
Let's hear it, what's going on?
-You hair grew 900 feet.
-[Christine] Thank you.
[Maya] I gotta tell you ladies,
after I left, I came home
with the baby, right?
I'm in sweatpants
and he's burping all over me,
with a ponytail and looking
like I didn't sleep,
and I open social media and I see
Christine in a boat, like, all fancy.
-I'm like, "That bitch."
-[Amanza laughing]
[Christine] You know,
I fell madly in love.
I was like, "Let's take a breather,
let's just travel the world," you know?
He's retired, obviously,
so it worked out great.
Obviously.
[Brett] Who's not retired at 35? Come on.
[Heather] Where has been
your favorite place and why?
-[Christine] I mean, Dubai was amazing.
-[Heather] Oh!
Bali was beautiful.
Indonesia was incredible, like,
it was just so many different experiences.
We didn't really have plans,
that was the best part of it.
We're just, like, "I think tomorrow
we should go to Maldives. I think..."
That sounds like a terrible way
to live your life.
You must have been so stressed.
It was so stressful!
Trying to plan my outfits.
The left hand looked extremely tired
because the freaking thing looks...
[Christine] This shit
is weighed down right now.
Yeah, so I didn't tell anyone.
-[Amanza] It's hard not to.
-[Christine] I mean...
[Amanza] How do you say no to this?
You said yes, right?
Where did you even meet him?
He was looking for a house, and so...
And instead he found a ho-- A wife.
Yeah, it was really nice.
I wasn't really expecting that.
-Did he end up buying the house?
-Yeah, he bought it for us.
So, I mean...
Davina told me you got engaged,
I was like, "What?"
I don't think I told anyone
for, like, three months, for um...
[Mary] Why?
Um...
Like, I waited to tell people
because I wanted to make sure
he was the one.
I heard about Christine getting engaged
not from Christine, but from Davina.
I mean news that big should have come
from my friend.
Not-- not from Davina.
It kind of hurt.
We've been together, like, nonstop
every second of the day--
When you travel with someone,
you become very close to them.
I mean, we were together 24/7.
I really didn't share my engagement
because I wanted to wait
'til I was back in the country.
I wanted to wait until I could, like,
show my ring and talk to people in person.
I didn't want to, like,
individually dial 900 people,
and have a copy-paste conversation.
Davina just happened to be the one person
I was in correspondence with at the time.
Davina was like,
"Oh, my God, that's so exciting."
It was over email though.
So I'm sure she was like...
"That's great.
Is the ring moissanite?"
[Christine chuckling]
Are you going to invite
Chrishell to the wedding?
What's going on with you guys, actually?
I haven't talked to her at all.
I reached out to her a few times.
When her father died,
I sent her flowers.
-That's nice.
-I sent her flowers for her birthday...
You know,
so I've been trying to reach out.
I think for the sake of the office
and the dynamic,
it would be nice if there would not be
any tension between the two of them,
but honestly, it's up to Christine.
If she doesn't go crazy again,
then we're good.
But with Christine, you just never know.
Time passes, it's been
a couple of months, so maybe...
I mean, we have two weddings.
-Maybe you guys can, you know...
-[Heather] Yeah.
Have a chat.
[Jason] Ladies, can we talk?
I want to go over
the twilight event at Hillside.
-Let's jump over here.
-[Davina] Yes.
[Chrishell] Driving around the Valley
and talking to contractors
and developers
has really consumed my day.
Tell them I'm the best one.
-If he asks.
-Okay, I will.
You need help to sell it
-before it even gets finished, right?
-Yeah.
Today was super promising.
But guess what,
developers love to ghost you.
So follow-through is everything.
You have to keep bugging them
and it's annoying, but it pays off.
If you get a chance, give me a call.
-Nice to meet you, Henry.
-Nice to meet you.
It was so nice to meet you.
If anyone else drops off their materials,
just throw them away.
[Chrishell] Where else can we go?
[Mary] You use
an old school calendar like this?
I'm old-school. I'm old-school.
I write checks actually, so...
That's what I said earlier and Heather
was like, "Who writes checks?"
I do. I pay all my bills.
I put it in an envelope, I stamp it...
-I used to be like that.
-Ladies, let's...
Oh, sorry.
We've gotta go over this twilight event
we're going to do for Hillside.
So we're coming on the market
at 43 million 900 thousand.
-That's the price that they put.
-Nice.
You guys can submit maybe your best
three to five clients you've got,
your wealthiest, most established clients,
we'll invite them to the event.
What I'm hoping you guys can do is
help walk all these clients
and brokers to the house.
-Have you guys all seen it?
-Has everyone seen it?
-Yeah.
-[Davina] Not, like, fully...
I haven't seen it since...
-I haven't it seen it recently.
-It's mind-blowing.
It's one of the top three homes
I've seen in my life.
I've seen a fair amount
of 100-million dollar homes.
So this event is really important
to the owner, Jeff,
and it's really important to us.
This night is probably
our best chance to sell this house.
I really want your A-game.
I want you to bring
all of your best clients.
I want everyone dressed sharp
and to know all about the house.
This has been three years in the making,
so this night is really important.
-So exciting!
-[Brett] It is. When you see the house...
It's like your baby, honestly.
It really is, yeah.
This is the only baby
you're ever gonna have.
[dog barking loudly]
Zelda, stop!
[dog barking fades]
-Woo! Not on my dress!
-[Jason] By the way...
Argh!
Zelda!
♪ I got something I gotta tell you ♪
♪ So get ready for another breakthrough ♪
♪ So let me show you what I mean... ♪
Oh, wow.
I love that everyone's going
to walk up to the car.
[Davina] Oh, wow!
[Heather] What a perfect night for this.
-It's so beautiful.
-[Maya] No power lines. Wow.
-[Jason] To selling.
-[all] To selling!
-[Heather] So many people suddenly.
-[Jason] I know.
[Jason] Guys, once you have drinks,
head this way, please.
[Amanza] Hey, don't stand
on the furniture.
Forty-three million dollar house.
-[Maya] Yeah, that's it.
-[woman] What's the square footage?
[Maya] Over 20,000.
[Jason] Let me walk you upstairs.
[Jason] The house is insane.
-Hiya, baby, good to see you.
-I'm great.
Baby, you're finally here.
-Finally. You took forever.
-How are you?
I know, they keep me away from you.
[Amanza] The first house I ever staged,
actually, was your house.
Yeah, like, six years ago or something.
[Heather] That's awesome.
Mary, I was telling them, you know,
I went to Miami for two months.
You're getting married,
Christine is engaged,
Hector is gonna get married
before you know it.
So, my boyfriend and I went to dinner
with Christine and Christian.
It was like a $3,000 dinner
and we were like, "Whoa."
They were ordering vintage champagne
and special caviar,
we were like, "Oh, okay..."
That's roughly $750 a person.
That's not a normal evening for me.
Mary, I was just telling Davina,
I love Christine, she's so fun and crazy,
and I heard Christian is
very calm and normal.
I can't wait to get to meet him.
I have no idea what to expect really.
I mean, she says she's happy.
That's all I've-- That's all I know.
[Maya] Are you excited at all?
Is Romain excited?
-Or is he like...
-Yeah.
We keep having to do new rules
on who's coming and who's not.
So we're still figuring it out.
I don't know.
So, how many people?
Sixty, something like that maybe.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
-Oh, my goodness.
-This is nice.
Okay, this is chill and Zen
and nice and calming, right?
[Heather] How are you feeling,
like, with you and Christine?
There's been a lot of drama
just because, you know.
-Obviously, you were there before.
-Yeah.
But there's been a lot of stuff
that's happened since then.
Has she been mean or what?
She had a party that everyone
was invited to but me.
Saying really ridiculous
things on Twitter,
making my dad's death about her, somehow.
[Chrishell] My dad passed
and he died from lung cancer, so...
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Sorry, I can't.
Sorry.
It's hard to talk-- I can't.
[sighs]
Okay. This is going to be
really hard to say out loud. Okay.
[sighs]
On one hand, you're devastated
that he's gone,
and on the other hand there's relief
because he was in so much pain.
So, it's just a bunch of emotions
and it's just been tough.
Sorry, what else did you ask me?
I knew she'd sent you flowers
for your dad passing and I was like,
"Oh, wow." Okay, they're
talking again, they're sweet.
I was like, "Great. This is great."
So, I don't know anything else
that happened. I just thought...
Then I came back from Sweden
and then I'm like,
"Wait, they're not friends."
Okay, I thought you guys...
[Chrishell] Yeah.
I just feel like she sells one story
to you guys, and then does stuff to me.
Then she always wants to be the good guy
with what she tells you,
she doesn't tell you all the stuff.
I don't want to get down in the mud
with her so I don't say it.
It brings me anxiety. I know she's coming.
I haven't even gone over all the different
things that have gone on with her.
So, at this point, I am definitely not
in a place where I'm going to...
try and have a conversation with her.
That is not something that would go well.
The tension between Chrishell
and Christine has been stressful.
Like, very, very stressful.
I'm gonna have anxiety now tonight.
Anticipating their arrival,
"Where is she? Where is her?"
♪ Waited so long
So close you can taste it ♪
I just got this today. It says,
-"Stress treatment, CBD roll on."
-Do it!
"For tranquility."
♪ Get ready for the ride of the year
Oh, no, no! ♪
[Chrishell] I need it.
-[both laughing]
-Fuck it.
I actually would prefer not to talk
to Christine tonight just because...
Again, I just don't know
what she's going to do.
I'm not great with confrontation
and the last time we were at
a social event
with everyone together, you know,
she completely humiliated me
in front of everybody,
and called me all kind of names
and screamed and yelled.
This cannot happen tonight.
This can't happen here.
[Chrishell] I don't want to talk to her.
[groans] I just...
It brings-- I don't know.
It just-- It makes me very flustered.
♪ Are you ready for it ♪
-[Maya] It is nice.
-[Davina] Oh, here's Christine, guys.
Hi!
Why does Christine always dress--
[Chrishell] I need to get a drink.
-[Maya] See ya.
-[Heather] Hi, honey!
-You look amazing!
-[Heather] You look like Marilyn Monroe.
You're so beautiful.
You look great. Are you excited?
I'm excited to see what's going
to happen tonight.
Aren't we all?
-Dun-dun-da!
-[Christine] Yeah.
♪ I know what you
I know what you came for ♪
♪ I'mma give you something
You can savor ♪
♪ For the rest of the night
I'll be blowing your mind ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ The woman that you waited for
Has gone bad ♪
♪ And I can guarantee
You're gonna love it ♪